const questionFetch = [
  {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is capital of Pakistan?",
      "options": [
          "Lahore",
          "Karachi",
          "Islamabad",
          "Quetta"
      ],
      "answer": "Islamabad"
  },
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Pakistan day celeberated on ?",
      "options": ["9-November", "14-August", "16-December", "23-March"],
      "answer": "23-March"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which of the following is the top IT University of Pakistan?",
      "options": ["COMSATS", "IIU", "FAST", "NUST"],
      "answer": "COMSATS"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Who is the number one teacher of Advanced Web?",
      "options": ["Amir Mehemmod", "Rana M. Ajmal", "Asif Shehzad", "Shehbaz Akhtar Abid"],
      "answer": "Rana M. Ajmal"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which mountain range is located in Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Andes", "Himalayas", "Alps", "Rockies"],
      "answer": "Himalayas"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What is the national flower of Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Rose", "Jasmine", "Tulip", "Sunflower"],
      "answer": "Jasmine"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which river is the longest in Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Indus", "Jhelum", "Chenab", "Ravi"],
      "answer": "Indus"
    },
    
    
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which city is known as the 'City of Gardens' in Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Karachi", "Lahore", "Islamabad", "Peshawar"],
      "answer": "Lahore"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which Province has the most mysterious mountains?",
      "options": ["KPK", "Balochistan", "Sindh", "Punjab"],
      "answer": "Balochistan"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which sea is located to the south of Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Arabian Sea", "Red Sea", "Mediterranean Sea", "Caspian Sea"],
      "answer": "Arabian Sea"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What is the national animal of Pakistan?",
      "options": ["Lion", "Markhor", "Snow Leopard", "Deer"],
      "answer": "Markhor"
    }
]

export default questionFetch;